{
  "id": "016-daily",
  "title": "Daily Routine",
  "questions": [
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "dirbu",
      "choices": [
        "I work",
        "I eat",
        "I go",
        "I sleep"
      ],
      "answer": "I work",
      "tts": "dirbu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "miegu",
      "choices": [
        "I sleep",
        "I wake",
        "I eat",
        "I go"
      ],
      "answer": "I sleep",
      "tts": "miegu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "valgau",
      "choices": [
        "I eat",
        "I drink",
        "I go",
        "I sleep"
      ],
      "answer": "I eat",
      "tts": "valgau"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "einu",
      "choices": [
        "I go",
        "I come",
        "I work",
        "I eat"
      ],
      "answer": "I go",
      "tts": "einu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "keliuosi",
      "choices": [
        "I wake up",
        "I sleep",
        "I eat",
        "I go"
      ],
      "answer": "I wake up",
      "tts": "keliuosi"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "dirbu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "miegu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "valgau"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "einu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "keliuosi"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "dirbu",
      "choices": [
        "I work",
        "I eat",
        "I go",
        "I sleep"
      ],
      "answer": "I work",
      "tts": "dirbu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "miegu",
      "choices": [
        "I sleep",
        "I wake",
        "I eat",
        "I go"
      ],
      "answer": "I sleep",
      "tts": "miegu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "valgau",
      "choices": [
        "I eat",
        "I drink",
        "I go",
        "I sleep"
      ],
      "answer": "I eat",
      "tts": "valgau"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "einu",
      "choices": [
        "I go",
        "I come",
        "I work",
        "I eat"
      ],
      "answer": "I go",
      "tts": "einu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "keliuosi",
      "choices": [
        "I wake up",
        "I sleep",
        "I eat",
        "I go"
      ],
      "answer": "I wake up",
      "tts": "keliuosi"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "dirbu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "miegu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "valgau"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "einu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "keliuosi"
    }
  ]
}